baseball-almanac.com 2019-11-05

# Baseball Almanac Privacy Policy

|  | 

### Baseball Almanac Privacy Policy

This privacy policy covers how Baseball Almanac, Inc. treats personal information that we collect and receive, including information related to your past use of Baseball Almanac, Inc. products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.  
  
---  
|  | 

"The greatest name in American sports history is Babe Ruth, a hitter." - Ted Williams  
  
---|---  
| Baseball Almanac Privacy Policy 

"Where what happened yesterday is being preserved today."  
  
---  
  
**Baseball Almanac Privacy Policy**  
  
Baseball Almanac, Inc. takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**NOTICE:[ Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/about-ftc/bureaus-offices/bureau-consumer-protection/our-divisions/division-privacy-and-identity) for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission.**

**Collection of Information**

  * Baseball Almanac, Inc. collects personal information when you register with [Baseball Fever](http://www.baseball-fever.com/), when you register for our newsletter, and when you buy a download or financially support our efforts to preserve the history of our national pastime. Baseball Almanac, Inc. does not combine information about you with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

  * Baseball Almanac, Inc., via our site host, receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested.

  * Baseball Almanac, Inc. uses information to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, and conduct research.

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information**

  * Baseball Almanac, Inc. does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.

    * We transfer information about you if Baseball Almanac, Inc.  is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

  * Baseball Almanac, Inc. displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies like Google & Burst Media) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria.

    * We do not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

  * Baseball Almanac, Inc. works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. For more information regarding providers of products or services and their policy please click their privacy links.

**Cookies**  

  * Baseball Almanac, Inc. may set and access cookies on your computer.

  * Baseball Almanac, Inc. lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to our cookies.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

  * Baseball Almanac, Inc. may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Questions and Suggestions**

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please visit our feedback page or you can contact us at:

Baseball Almanac, Inc.  
Privacy Policy Issues  
8263 SW 107 Avenue, Apt A.  
Miami, FL 33173 

Effective Date: April 1, 2005. Major Changes. August 19, 2007. Last Updated March 26, 2014.  
  
**Baseball Almanac Privacy Policy**  

|  |   
---|---|---  
| 

Baseball Almanac, Inc. uses third-party advertising companies (specifically Google, Inc.) to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice, and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, opting out options, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Usenet news groups, spiders and robots may retrieve your public / viewable username; however, [Baseball Fever](http://www.baseball-fever.com/) is safe and your identity is encrypted on the server as well as your IP address and email address.

Our advertising agencies/partners (Burst Media & Google) were selected by Baseball Almanac, Inc. due to their important stance taken on security and privacy.

|   
|  |
